The last month has been very interesting for me.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And part of the reason is because of Essence Magazine and an op-ed that was published.
Tomorrow on Small Doses Podcast, I'll be interviewing the editor-in-chief of Essence Magazine, Carolyn Wenga, in side effects of clearing the air.
If you would like to have your questions considered to be asked in this very unique and exclusive episode, please subscribe to my Patreon.
You'll also possibly get the opportunity to watch the episode recorded live.
Yes, that's right.
Side effects of clearing the air with Essence Magazine is coming soon on Small Doses Podcast.
If you want to have your questions considered, subscribe to Patreon, Amanda Seals.